A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Administration File, 3; 110.4 Cubic Feet Boxes 204-479.
    - Berelson, Bernard - Office of the President - Reviews - Tarrytown Meeting, 1972 December (Box 414, Folder 3974)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Office of the President - Reviews - Technical Assistance Division, 1974 August 29 (Box 414, Folder 3975)
    - Berelson, Bernard - Office of the President - Reviews - Warwick, 1977 January (Box 414, Folder 3976)
    - Balfour, Marshall, 1967-1968 (Box 300, Folder 2759)
    - Balfour, Marshall - McMichael Visit, 1967 (Box 300, Folder 2760)
    - Balfour, Marshall - Diary Notes, 1963-1968 (Box 301, Folder 2761)
    - Balfour, Marshall - Memos, 1967-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2762)
    - Balfour, Marshall - Travel - Asia, 1970 (Box 301, Folder 2763)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - Bellagio IV Meetings, 1977 June (Box 388, Folder 3770)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - Bellagio IV, 1976-1979 (Box 388, Folder 3771)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - Bureau of Oceans and International Environmental and Scientific Affairs, 1978 (Box 388, Folder 3772)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - East-West Communication Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 388, Folder 3773)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - IBM Seminar - "Population, Employment and Change", 1977 (Box 388, Folder 3774)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - IPPF/UNFPA/PC Meeting, London, 1979 May 30-31 (Box 388, Folder 3775)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - East-West Communication Institute - Conference on Population Communications: Synthesis and Prospects, 1977 February 27 - March 5; 2015:FA432:012; 1 print. (Box 11A)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - India, 1976-1977 (Box 388, Folder 3776)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - National Academy of Sciences - Conference on Population, 1977-1979 (Box 388, Folder 3777)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - Tokyp International Symposium, 1976-1977 (Box 388, Folder 3778)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - Twenty-Five Year Chronicle, 1978-1979 (Box 389, Folder 3779)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - Woods Hole Meeting - Program Review Notes, 1976 (Box 389, Folder 3780)
    - Bausch, James J. - Office of the Vice President and Treasurer - World Bank, 1977-1978 (Box 389, Folder 3781)
    - Bean, Lee L., 1968-1971 (Box 301, Folder 2764)
    - Bean, Lee L. - Virginia's Environmental Teach-in Program, 1970 (Box 301, Folder 2765)
    - Bean, Lee L. - Diary Notes, 1968-1971 (Box 301, Folder 2766)
    - Bean, Lee L. - Memos, 1968-1973 (Box 301, Folder 2767)
    - Bean, Lee L. - Speeches Articles, 1968-1969 (Box 301, Folder 2768)
    - Bean, Lee L. - Travel, 1971-1972 (Box 301, Folder 2769)
    - Belsky, Ray, 1967-1971 (Box 301, Folder 2770)
    - Belsky, Ray - Diary Notes, 1969 (Box 302, Folder 2771)
    - Belsky, Ray - Memos, 1967-1971 (Box 302, Folder 2772)
      Includes material on Dr. Katherine Kuder, dated August 1969.
    - Blaydes, Robert M., 1969 (Box 302, Folder 2773)
    - Burch, Thomas, 1970; 1972 (Box 302, Folder 2774)
    - Burch, Thomas - Memos, 1970-1972 (Box 302, Folder 2775)
    - Caldwell, J. C., 1967-1969 (Box 302, Folder 2776)
    - Caldwell, J. C. - Pending - Search for Demographers for African Universities, 1968 (Box 302, Folder 2777)
    - Caldwell, J. C. - Diary Notes, 1968 (Box 302, Folder 2778)
    - Caldwell, J. C. - Memos, 1967-1968 (Box 302, Folder 2779)
    - Caldwell, J. C. - Trip Reports, 1973 (Box 302, Folder 2780)
    - Castadot, Robert - Memos, 1971-1974 (Box 302, Folder 2781)
    - Chappel, Martha - Memos, 1969 (Box 303, Folder 2782)
    - Chen, Phillip - Memos, 1970-1971 (Box 303, Folder 2783)
    - Danziger, Sanford - Memos, 1969 (Box 303, Folder 2784)
    - Demeny, Paul - Memos, 1973 (Box 303, Folder 2785)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Algeria, 1971-1976 (Box 415, Folder 3977)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh, 1974-1976 (Box 415, Folder 3978)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh - Trip, 1974 (Box 415, Folder 3979)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh - Papers and Reports, 1974 (Box 415, Folder 3980)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh - Papers and Reports, 1974 (Box 415, Folder 3981)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh - Papers and Reports, 1974 (Box 415, Folder 3982)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh - Papers and Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 416, Folder 3983)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh, 1974 (Box 416, Folder 3984)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh, 1974 (Box 416, Folder 3985)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Bangladesh - Bangladesh Institute of Development Economics - PSC/BIDS Meeting (Box 416, Folder 3986)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Chile, 1971 (Box 416, Folder 3987)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - China, 1973-1974 (Box 416, Folder 3988)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Colombia, 1974-1976 (Box 416, Folder 3989)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - India, 1973-1976 (Box 416, Folder 3990)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - India - Ramakrishna Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 416, Folder 3991)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Indonesia, 1973-1976 (Box 417, Folder 3992)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Mojokerto Project, 1975 (Box 417, Folder 3993)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Iran, 1974-1975 (Box 417, Folder 3994)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Iran, 1973-1974 (Box 417, Folder 3995)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Kenya, 1969-1974 (Box 417, Folder 3996)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Korea, 1975 (Box 417, Folder 3997)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Korea, 1970-1976 (Box 417, Folder 3998)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Nigeria, 1973-1976 (Box 417, Folder 3999)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Pakistan, 1974-1975 (Box 418, Folder 4000)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Pakistan, 1970-1975 (Box 418, Folder 4001)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Philippines, 1974-1975 (Box 418, Folder 4002)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Taiwan, 1975-1976 (Box 418, Folder 4003)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Taiwan, 1970-1973 (Box 418, Folder 4004)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Taiwan, 1969-1974 (Box 418, Folder 4005)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Tanzania, 1974-1976 (Box 419, Folder 4006)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Tanzania - PC Agreement with Government, 1972-1973 (Box 419, Folder 4007)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Thailand, 1972-1973 (Box 419, Folder 4008)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Thailand - Bangkok, 1970-1975 (Box 419, Folder 4009)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Tunisia, 1969-1975 (Box 419, Folder 4010)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Turkey, 1970-1976 (Box 419, Folder 4011)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - USSR, 1975 (Box 419, Folder 4012)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Country Files - Vietnam, 1970; 1972 (Box 419, Folder 4013)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - A-Z, 1974 (Box 419, Folder 4014)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - Brown University, 1973-1974 (Box 419, Folder 4015)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - Duke University, 1973 (Box 419, Folder 4016)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - Harvard University - School of Public Health, 1973-1976 (Box 419, Folder 4017)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - MIT - Center for International Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 419, Folder 4018)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - University of Michigan - Population Studies Center, 1973-1975 (Box 419, Folder 4019)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - University of North Carolina - University Population Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 420, Folder 4020)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - Princeton - Office of Population Research, 1974-1976 (Box 420, Folder 4021)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - Stanford University - Food Research Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 420, Folder 4022)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Universities - University of Washington (Seattle) - Modernization and the Balkan Peasant, 1969-1976 (Box 420, Folder 4023)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United States Agency for International Development (USAID), 1972-1976 (Box 420, Folder 4024)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - American Economic Association (AEA), 1973-1976 (Box 420, Folder 4025)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Batelle, 1973-1974 (Box 420, Folder 4026)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Brookings Institute, 1974 (Box 420, Folder 4027)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Bush Foundation, 1974 (Box 420, Folder 4028)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Center for Family Planning Program Development (Planned Parenthood-World Population), 1973 (Box 420, Folder 4029)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Committee for International Coordination of National Research in Demography (CICRED) (Box 420, Folder 4030)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 420, Folder 4031)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 421, Folder 4032)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 421, Folder 4033)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 421, Folder 4034)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 421, Folder 4035)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 421, Folder 4036)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 422, Folder 4037)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - CICRED (Box 422, Folder 4038)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Council on Foreign Relations, 1973-1976 (Box 422, Folder 4039)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - East-West Council, 1973-1976 (Box 422, Folder 4040)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - East-West Council, 1972-1973 (Box 422, Folder 4041)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Ford Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 422, Folder 4042)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Ford Foundation, 1968-1973 (Box 423, Folder 4043)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Ford Foundation/Rockefeller Foundation - Population Policy Research Program, 1975 (Box 423, Folder 4044)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - General Electric Company, 1975 (Box 423, Folder 4044A)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - HEW (Department of) - National Institutes of Health, 1970-1971 (Box 423, Folder 4045)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - HEW (Department of) - National Institutes of Health, 1970-1971 (Box 423, Folder 4046)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Instittute of Urban and Regional Development (UC-Berkeley), 1976 (Box 423, Folder 4047)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - International Development Research Center, 1970-1975 (Box 423, Folder 4048)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - International Institute for Educational Planning, 1972 (Box 424, Folder 4049)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - International Institute of Applied Systems Analysis (Vienna), 1976 (Box 424, Folder 4050)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population (IUSSP) - General Assembly, 1973-1975 (Box 424, Folder 4051)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - IUSSP - Studies and Reports (Box 424, Folder 4052)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - IUSSP - Studies and Reports (Box 424, Folder 4053)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - IUSSP - Studies and Reports (Box 424, Folder 4054)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - IUSSP - Economics Subcommittee, 1972-1974 (Box 424, Folder 4055)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Korean Institute for Research in the Behavioral Sciences (KIRBS), 1973-1974 (Box 424, Folder 4056)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1974 (Box 424, Folder 4057)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - National Science Foundation, 1973 (Box 424, Folder 4058)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD), 1973-1974 (Box 425, Folder 4059)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Planned Parenthood, 1974-1975 (Box 425, Folder 4060)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Population Association of America (PAA), 1970-1976 (Box 425, Folder 4061)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Population Crisis Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 425, Folder 4062)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Population Reference Bureau, 1974-1976 (Box 425, Folder 4063)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Rockefeller Commission (Commission on Critical Choices for Americans), 1974-1975 (Box 425, Folder 4064)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Rockefeller Foundation, 1968-1976 (Box 425, Folder 4065)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - SIMS (Thomsen), 1974 (Box 425, Folder 4066)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - Smithsonian Institute, 1964-1975 (Box 425, Folder 4067)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - State Department, 1974 (Box 425, Folder 4068)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Renselaerville/Aspen Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 426, Folder 4069)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Economic and Social Council - Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 426, Folder 4070)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Economic and Social Council - Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 426, Folder 4071)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Economic and Social Council - Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 426, Folder 4072)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Economic and Social Council - Reports, 1959-1972 (Box 426, Folder 4073)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Escape, 1972 (Box 427, Folder 4074)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Escape, 1972 (Box 427, Folder 4075)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Escape, 1969-1972 (Box 427, Folder 4076)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Escape, 1969-1972 (Box 427, Folder 4077)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - UNESCO (Box 427, Folder 4078)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - UNESCO (Box 428, Folder 4079)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - FAO (Box 428, Folder 4080)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - FAO (Box 428, Folder 4081)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - UNFPA, 1974-1976 (Box 428, Folder 4082)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - International Labor Office, 1971-1976 (Box 428, Folder 4083)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - International Statistical Institute (Box 428, Folder 4084)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Statistical Office - Demographic Yearbook, 1973-1976 (Box 429, Folder 4085)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - United Nations - Union Douaniere Et Economique de L'Afrique Centrale, 1974 (Box 429, Folder 4086)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - University of Sussex - Institute of Development Studies, 1976 (Box 429, Folder 4087)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - World Bank, 1972-1975 (Box 429, Folder 4088)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - World Fertility Survey, 1974 (Box 429, Folder 4089)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - World Fertility Survey - WFS Committee - Burch, Seltzer, 1974-1976 (Box 429, Folder 4090)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - World Population Plan of Action - Latin America, 1974-1976 (Box 430, Folder 4091)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Organizations - World Population Society, 1974 (Box 430, Folder 4092)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Summer Internships, 1976 (Box 431)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted from access.
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Summer Internships, 1975 (Box 431)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Summer Internships, 1974 (Box 431)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Fellowships (Box 432)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Budget (Box 432)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Grants - Accounting (Box 432)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Grants - Demeny Correspondence (Box 433)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Grants - Reorganization (Box 433)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Visitors, 1973-1976 (Box 430, Folder 4093)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Staff Seminars, 1973-1976 (Box 430, Folder 4094)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Inter-Office Memos, 1973-1976 (Box 430, Folder 4095)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Projects, 1974-1976 (Box 430, Folder 4096)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Projects - Age at Marriage Project, 1974-1975 (Box 430, Folder 4097)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Projects - Factbook, 1974-1975 (Box 430, Folder 4098)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Projects - Frejka - Country Projects, 1974-1975 (Box 430, Folder 4099)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Projects - Satellite Project, 1974 (Box 430, Folder 4100)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Proposed Workshop on Fertility and the Economics of Households, 1974 (Box 430, Folder 4101)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Staff Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 430, Folder 4102)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Annual Report 1975, 1976 (Box 434, Folder 4103)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Annual Report 1974, 1974-1975 (Box 434, Folder 4104)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Annual Report 1974 - Drafts, 1974-1975 (Box 434, Folder 4105)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Annual Report 1973, 1973-1974 (Box 434, Folder 4106)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Demographic Book List, 1973-1974 (Box 434, Folder 4107)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Demographic Book List in French, 1971-1973 (Box 434, Folder 4108)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1975 March (Box 434, Folder 4109)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1974 December (Box 434, Folder 4110)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1974 September (Box 434, Folder 4111)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1974 March (Box 434, Folder 4112)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report - Drafts, 1974 (Box 434, Folder 4113)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1976 June (Box 434, Folder 4114)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1976 March (Box 435, Folder 4115)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1975 December (Box 435, Folder 4116)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1975 June; September (Box 435, Folder 4117)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Activities Report, 1975 June (Box 435, Folder 4118)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Rotating Materials, 1974-1976 (Box 435, Folder 4119)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Work Plans 1975, 1974-1976 (Box 435, Folder 4120)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - AAAS, Mexico City, 1973 June (Box 435, Folder 4121)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Asian Population Conference Seminar (Second) (Box 435, Folder 4122)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Asian Population Conference Seminar (Second) (Box 436, Folder 4123)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Bangladesh Population and Development Workshop, NY, 1975 May (Box 436, Folder 4124)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Bellagio Conference, 1973 January (Box 436, Folder 4125)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Bellagio Conference, 1972 (Box 436, Folder 4126)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Bellagio Conference, 1973 (Box 436, Folder 4127)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IEA Conference papers, 1973 September (Box 437, Folder 4128)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IEA Conference papers, 1973 September (Box 437, Folder 4129)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IEA Conference papers, 1973 September (Box 437, Folder 4130)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IEA Conference papers, 1973 September (Box 437, Folder 4131)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IEA Conference papers, 1973 September (Box 438, Folder 4132)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IEA Conference - Valescure, 1973 September (Box 438, Folder 4133)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IUSSP General Conference, Liege, 1973 August (Box 438, Folder 4134)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IUSSP General Conference, Liege, 1973 August (Box 438, Folder 4135)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - IUSSP General Conference, Liege, 1973 August (Box 438, Folder 4135A)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Middle Eastern Population Policy Seminar, 1973 (Box 438, Folder 4136)
    - Demeny, Paul - Demographic Division - Conferences - Middle Eastern Population Policy Seminar, 1973 (Box 439, Folder 4137)